You are in from 4, 3, 2, 1.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Well then, be well.
Okay.
Let's go. Please do.
Can I do my regular thing to get into the swing of things?
It's been a while.
Let's join forces and go, go, go!
Hello! Hello!
It's live. Real time. Real time. Of course, this also means that we are transmitting to the whole world, as well as to those who are watching now. That's what it means.
In the language of each country. It's the World Wide Web! It's the world wide web. Thank you very much.
You never know, you may be in a country where you don't understand Japanese, but you may be told, "Hey, these guys are funny. Or, "He's so cute! No, not at all.
So, that's how it is.
Okay, well, let's see...16...uh...that's it...that's it. It's a shift-barricade!
It's a way of being exposed.
I've been called Tononaka lately, and anyway, I've been called cute Nakamura, so...
Well then, I'd like to start the recording.
So, don't you sometimes feel a little cold these days?
Yes, I do.
When you carelessly wear short sleeves...
Oh no!
It's cold!
It all happened so fast.
Come to think of it, summer wasn't so bad either.
Everybody's collapsed.
Good evening.
Like a katakana.
I thought you were a little thick.
Like Kokusho.Coxsone and all that.
No, no, no, no, no.
Motion is still good.
Kokusho or something already.
He's not that bad.
No, no, no, no, no.
He was a good guy.
You know what?
He got into a lot of fights.
Yes, we did.
I worked up a good sweat.
It's finally fall.
It's easier to spend time in the fall.
Yes, it is.
I'm glad.
And crickets, which Varigata loves, are everywhere.
I can't help but have an appetite for them.
That's what autumn means, isn't it?
Autumn is the season of appetite.
Appetite fall
Autumn of appetite
Eat by yourself
Maybe that's the most nourishing.
He said it's good for the breath
Don't eat, everyone... all of a sudden
Don't eat it.
I don't think there are many people like that.
So, I'll tell you what.
First of all, a word of wisdom.First of all, a word of wisdom.
I'd like to say something.
Mike Tyson...
The professional boxer.
Yes, sir.
I've heard of him.
He was a professional boxer.
He was very strong.
He's very famous.
Yes.
By the way, I didn't know him until today.
He was the same age as me.
What?
The exact same age.
Oh, wow.
I was born on May 10th, a little over a month ago.
In the U.S.
Tyson was born.
Oh, wow.
And this guy...
You know...
He was really strong, but...
But...
His height...
He's a heavyweight.
It's the highest division.
In heavyweight boxing...
If you weigh over 90 kilograms...
What's the weight limit?
For example, 200 kilograms is fine.Or 200 kilos, for example.
I don't know.
I mean...
What do you call it?
If it's fixed...
If you don't waver...
I'm the best.
Oh, my God!
The most fearsome, the most powerful.
Yes, sir
It's a hell of a place
So, you see...
Physically speaking, Japanese are a bit...
Heavyweight is a bit too much for them.
Yes, yes, yes.
You have to be...
You have to be big.
That's right.
That's the original...
That's why...
And then...
I'm about 5'5".
About 178 centimeters.
He's almost the same height as me.
I see.
I'm about the same height as him.
I'd probably be in the heavyweight division.
Most of them are big guys.
Ah...
We're going to beat them up.We're going to beat the crap out of those people.
Oh.
I see.
Anyway.
You're fast.
Punching.
The punch...
I feel like I'm going crazy.
It was like, "Bang, bang!
You know...
Almost all of them...
KOs in the first round.
Really?
Amazing.
Yes.
Even back then...
I thought it was amazing.
Anyway, I used to...
I used to watch gymnastics.
I was...
Before I knew what was going on.
It was already over.
You're that strong?
He's that strong?
He was really strong.
Yes.
Just a little.
His personal life was a little...
I was a little violent.
Oh.Ah.
I see.
Not so much.
I'm sure there'll be more later.
There were some problems...
But...
I see.
Well, anyway, I was impressed.
If it were a vox...
I'd say he's number one.
Oh, wow.
Like this.
This is the style.
It's called the peekaboo style.
That's right.
Like this.
So...
It's a famous analogy.
Mike Tyson's punch.
Was scientifically verified
The Mike Tyson punch.
Yes, sir.
And then...
It's like being hit with a grand piano
It's about the same as being hit by a grand piano.
as being hit by a grand piano.
Lift up the grand piano.
That's amazing.That's great.
So it's the same as doing a "bang"?
But you know what?
That would kill you.
That's true.
That's enough.
I don't know.
Anyway...
That's what the science guy said.
Well...
Well, the point is...
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know what it is.
So...
That's it.
You're a punching bag.
I've always had it.
No, it's amazing.
I don't know.
Like this...
Even the old people...
It's amazing.
It's like a movie.
Heh...
New York.
I grew up in a very poor neighborhood.
Mm-hmm.
And I was always getting into fights.
I just happened to come across it.I just happened to be there.
Someone happened to be watching.
He thought, "This guy's a badass.
I introduced him to a boxer.
Heh.
And after that
He got really strong.
They're going to start a movie.
He's a world champion.
Oh, wow.
Heh.
Mike Tyson.
Tyson.
Tyson
Mr. Mike Tyson
Mr. Tyson said...
May I?
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, sir.
If you met me in that last century, I'd be terrified of you myself right now.
Wow. I wish I could say that.
Well, you're probably right. I was 19, 20, 21, 22, 23...
I was great at that time. And you know what?
Boxing is only once every 6 months now, right? It's like a match every six months.
He was fighting every month. He's very strong, and he'd probably knock him out in the first round.
He says he doesn't think he's damaged that much.
There are rumors.
He was a great champion.He was a hell of a champion. So cool.
It's amazing that you're strong enough to be afraid of yourself. Amazing.
On the other hand, you were strong. Really strong.
Well, well, well... that's not why I'm here.
And now...
Let's try this.
Massage machines are... pretty common these days.
You can find them in public bathhouses.
I found an interesting massage machine.
A commuter rapid train at night in Suginami Ward, Tokyo
In the waiting room of Hachinohe Station in Aomori Prefecture
There was a massage machine with the same coloring as the Shinkansen.
So, that's it.
It's that thing you know, the Hayakusa-esque
This kind of
The color is amazing!
This is nice. Beautiful.
I think it's going to open up here.
I guess it'll fit in there.
It looks like this from the inside.
The legs are just like this.
Wow, that's how it's supposed to be.
It opens up like this.
Like this, and then you sit down.
Wow, and right in front of it are the train tracks.
It's right above the station.
Yes, that's where the bullet train comes through.
Amazing!
Great massage!
A zero-gravity massage.Weightless Massage
King Amma
King Amma?
King Amma.
King Amma... and she's four.
Four is great.
I think 1, 2, and 3 are probably going to be very, very popular, too.
Yeah, it's evolved and evolved.
And now...
Aomori...
He sent me a nice picture of Hokkaido.
Mr. Middle-aged rider!
Thank you very much!
Hokkaido's roads.
Anyway, can I have a picture too?
They're super straight.
There's nothing there.
Mountains.
The beginning of a movie like this.
Or a karaoke image like this.
The lyrics appear below.
Here Polar Body, huh?
And then the title comes up.
It's like this, isn't it?
It really exists, doesn't it?
In Japan.
It's like Hokkaido.
Amazing!
It's really straight.
It would be fun to ride a motorcycle on it.It would be fun to ride a motorcycle or something.
I'll ride a motorcycle.
It's like this, isn't it?
So close, so close!
Squeezing the handlebars
Buu bui bui is done.
And you know what else?
Let's talk about food.
How about this?
Monger.
It was moving fast, but there's something wrong with it.
The way he does it, he moves fast.
But it's kind of linear.
Like he said.
but his joints don't bend very well.
I like Monger.
I love monger.
I do it at home.
That's nice.
By yourself.
Yes, I like that.
On a hot plate.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
What's a monger?
Ropoli sent me your shopping skills, too.
Monjersha.
You call it mongersha?
I had the Mentaiko Mochi Cheese Monger in Asakusa
that's what it's calledSo.
I was wondering what your favorite type of monger type is.
Here's a picture.
When I look at it like this...
I feel a little sorry for one type of monger.
I feel a little sorry for him.
If I were in his shoes...
I don't feel sorry for him.
It doesn't look good.
That's right.
Even though it's delicious.
It's best before it's served.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's true.
This is a little...
It's like...
It's a monger.
This is... this is... this is... this is... this is...
It's an open monger.
That's right.
We'll do this again.
Separate them.
That's right.
By the way, how do you put it up?
First of all, I'd like to explain how to make it.First of all, I'd like to explain how to make it.
I heard there are various ways to make it.
Look, they're making a bank.
Yes, yes, yes.
Make a bank.
Put the soup inside.
And then...
We can even put a side dish on top.
That's right.
How do you make it?
We make a solid bank.
The bank, of course.
This powder inside...
You put it in two or three times.
And the box.
And then...
Oh, this one.
Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock.
Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock.
You do it often.
Yes, I do.
People in that line of work do it.
Like this.
Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock.
That's why...
It's really hot, isn't it?It's a little too hot, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
When you eat
There's one thing...
A little more
It could be a little cooler.
From a cat's tongue point of view...
That's right, isn't it?
It's normal to get burned, isn't it?
That's right.
But if you let it cool down, it doesn't taste good.
That's the other thing.
It's hard to find the right temperature.
What a hurdle, monger, all kinds of things.
Maybe it's deep.
No no no no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
By the way, I like something
something
Kind of
Hmmm...
This is the very one
Mentaiko Mochi Cheese Monger
Yes, he is!
It's a classic.
A classic.
A classic of all classics.
Everyone loves it.
I see.I see.
You have a barrica and something like that?
Something like that.
Put mentaiko (cod roe) in it.
Yes, sir.
Baby Star Ramen.
Crumble it up and put it in.
Oh!
It's delicious.
That's my favorite.
Baby Star Ramen.
I've heard rumors.
It's really good.
Delicious!
I don't know...
Don't you eat it when it's cold?
I've been to Tokyo, but...
Not really.
Really?
Anyway, if you have a cat's tongue...
Monjer and koronbao...
Oh...
Well...
I'm sorry.
It's fine if you're eating alone.
Maybe...
Maybe I should just say no.
We're all doing it together.
I'm all of a sudden...
At the monger.At Monger.
If you're wowed...
I'd hate it.
You're right.
I'm sorry about that.
It's too hot not to come in.
No, but it sure is hot, isn't it?
By the way, what do you have?
I'm surprised that there are flavors like ume shiso (plum and shiso paste).
It's refreshing and tasty.
Or...
There's also a squid smelt monger.
I like squid smelt!
I like that Mr. Moheiji.
I like that monger called Moheiji.
You can find them in many places.
I like that kind of thing there.
I like the ume and shiso kind.
And squid smelling monger.
I really like it there.
I can't get enough of squid smelt.
It's delicious!
It's been a while since I've had pasta with squid meat.
I was so impressed when I had it.
It looks kind of...
It's all black.
Yes, it is pitch black.
And yet, what's that flavor?
It has a rich taste.
It's very rich.It's got a heavy richness to it.
The best part of squid is concentrated there.
Yes, it is, isn't it?
I think it's wonderful.
That's what I meant.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
The Monger Company
And by the way...
Um...
Hanamichi is finally old enough to get a driver's license.
He's 18 now.
And we were talking about cars.
If Hanamichi gets his license
I sent him a picture of what it might look like
He sent me a picture of what he imagined
He sent me a picture.
Let's see...
Yoshinari Aoi
Shinagawa Kawasaki
Thank you very much.
I got a car license.
I painted the flower path I drove down.
Yes, sir.
So...
Like this.
A Mercedes Benz.
He's tipping it over.
And he hit the signboard.
Well, you know, Hanamichi...
He said he wanted a Mercedes.You said you wanted a Mercedes.
You're saying that, right?
You want a car?
Yeah, a Mercedes. Yeah, a Mercedes.
You did say that.
You did say that, didn't you?
That's right.
For my generation...
Mercedes-Benz cars weren't fashionable.
Mercedes-Benz wasn't so fashionable in the past.
It was more...
I don't know how to say it.
It was a bit hidden
That's right, that's right.
The Mercedes Benz logo...
This kind of mark...
It's like...
At the very tip of the hood
In the middle of the hood.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's totally different now.
Now
It's so cool!
It's stylish now, isn't it?
Yes.
He's so much cooler now.
And you know what else?
A friend of mine...
He runs a company.
I've been riding since I was young.I've ridden a lot since I was young.
For example...
What's that?
Well, Mercedes is one of them.
And what's that?
What's that company?
BMW
Yes, yes, yes, a company.
Renault...
Salt...
You know, something like...
Alfa Lorre...
Volvo...
Volvos.
I only got one.
The guy who got in said it was a Mercedes.
That's right.
Very comfortable to drive and use.
Oh, I see.
It's something...
Well, you know...
Everyone has their own taste.
I can't say it's a one-size-fits-all solution.
But it has a lot of potential.
That's true.
It's tough... if something like this happens.
That's where you'd come in.
That's where I'd go.
Hanamichi.
Hanamichi.He's going to do it, isn't he?
He's gonna do it.
It's really scary.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm here in the Mercedes.
I'm here in a Mercedes.
Let me guess.
Give me a picture of the accident.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes, yes, yes.
By the way...
That middle-aged rider...
He sent me a picture of Hokkaido and some text.
It's amazing!
It's Japan's largest soba production area.
I heard there's a place called Horokanai in Hokkaido.
There's a place in Hokkaido called Horokanai.
Soba field
Yes, it's called Horokanai.
Soba fields in Honshu
Yes, sir.
The scale of the field is different from that of Honshu.
So the area must be huge!
Wow!
This is all buckwheat!
Amazing!
All soba noodles!
Wow!
Wow!I don't know.
I wonder how much I can do with this.
Wow!
How many servings of soba noodles can I make?
How many servings?
Seriously, don't you think this is a little difficult?
I wonder how many servings
How many servings can we make?
That's amazing!
This is amazing!
I wonder if we're just going to buy it all at once.
Yeah.
How do you make it?
I wonder. The meat is like this.
You take it off, and then you pull out the black grains, and that's how it looks like.
It's amazing.
I really like standing-only noodle restaurants, don't you?
Maybe I am happy that there are so many things I like.
What kind of things would you put in a field if it was full of barigatas or something like that?
Monja.
So you like monja.
Monja field. It's possible.
The name is, there is a monja field, and it is the largest producer of monja in Japan.
No, no, no.
That's not how it grows.
How does it grow? It's a sludge, isn't it?
Eh, it's a bit surly.
Eh, I wonder.
I want to see a field like this.
I want to see a field like this.I would like to see a field like this.
Food.
Yes, I would. If so, I would have to say crab cream croquettes.
So, I want to tell you both that this is not a corner to say what I like.
Am I wrong?
Sure, I said I like buckwheat noodles, but I said it's the raw material.
Shouldn't it be the raw material?
For example, if you like udon, you see wheat.
So, let's say, it's rice, right?
I like sake, so when I see rice, I think, "Wow, I hope it will become good sake.
The rice paddies, just before harvest, are really beautiful, aren't they? It is really beautiful, isn't it?
The rice fields are beautiful, aren't they?
Rice paddies are beautiful. They are so smooth, like this.
When the wind blows, it's like a wave.
It feels like Japan.
So, let's have another barikata. I thought Monger was just here for the comedy.
Yes, that's right.
Let's leave it here.
Yes, let's leave it here.
You mean the name of the ingredients, right?
Ingredient name.
Baby Star Ramen Hatake.
Ah, ingredients.
When I say ingredients, it doesn't mean that's what it's become, too.
Wow, it's a Baby Star field.
Idiot.
I wonder why. How do you harvest it, besides.
Oh, is it long?
Is it long?
It's pretty long, take it and fold it at home.It's pretty long, and you take it and fold it at home.
It's like folding and straightening.
Oh, you take it straight. As it is.
They have a bit of a salty taste to them, too.
Amazing, Hatake. I knew it.
Really.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well.
I'm going to start live delivery soon.
Last week, I was hoping to get it.
I was hoping to have it last week, but I wanted to do the "screentime" that we used to do.
I asked them to pose for a few seconds.
I asked them to pose for a few seconds, and then I asked them to tell me how many seconds they had.
And that was very well received.
That was also very well received.
Well, that's true.
But there were a lot of problems, such as, "Is there really any need for me to have my own photo shoot time?
I was told, "No, you don't." Why?
Why not?
Yes.
Well, I still have to go first.
Oh, I see.
I'm looking for something.
Something like... Oh, this, then.
Oh, that's good.
A mini-master.
Oh, it's the same.
They look exactly the same.
Yes, it is.
May I?Is that okay?
Yes, I mean it.
Pause your serve.
Yes, sir.
And can you look at me for the camera, please? You look like a man who knows what he's doing.
You know, you can move a computer around like this.
Computer.
So... how do you want to do it?
We do photo shoots in episodes.
Do they often ask you to pose?
What kind of pose?
What do you have in mind?
The customary way.
Oh, but it's a lot of splitting, a lot of splitting.
Okay, then.
Stop once at the burr.
Stop once at the shoulder.
Shall we do three shots in a row?
Yes, that's right.
Let's start with the first one.
Bari...
Next, shoulders.
Shoulder.
Burr and shoulder.
They're the same, they're the same.
They're the same.
And finally...
Yes, sir.
No, no, no.No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The side that went this way.
Yes, sir.
Got it.
Good bye.
Yes, ma'am.
See you at 718.
See you next week.
Next week
7:00 p.m.
Hey, you're an hour early.
Why?
Why 7:00 p.m.?
Well, I'm on a bit of a recording schedule.
Woooo!
Huh?
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I'm really into it.
Woooo!
It's like Boeing.
I don't know.
Maybe there's something different about it all the time.
Oh, my.
Huh?
Maybe.
I don't understand.I don't understand.
Something.
Like someone's coming.
Maybe.
Ehhhh...
Who's coming?
Who is it?
I don't know...
Yes, I am
And that's why
Yes, sir.
I'll see you next week.
Thank you very much for this week.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much